(Howard:)Yeah. We, uh, made gift bags, had wine...
(Howard:)...and then went online and saw this.
Of all the "Howard humping hooker" stories...
...that one's my favorite.
(Raj:)You know, we're not that far
from my apartment.
(Raj:)If you stop the car, I can walk from here.
You ain't going anywhere, Threeway.
(Howard:)Bernadette, listen...
You lied. You said you told me
about all the girls you've been with...
(Bernadette:)...but you never mentioned
your cousin, the prostitute or Raj.
(Raj:)Seriously, you don't
even have to stop the car.
Anything under 10 miles an hour
and I can combat-roll into the street.
(Howard:)Okay, just to set the record straight...
...l didn't hire the prostitute,
she was a gift from him.
(Howard:)Shame on you, Raj. That is not how
we treat women in this country.
(Bernadette:)Don't you try and blame this on him.
(Sheldon:)- Thank you.
- Zip it, pervert!